So you'll notice that inside of the project, we have two basically two different data types.
We have the restaurant, we have dishes.
And so just like the restaurant card where we added prop types to the dish,
we need you to do the same for the dish.
And so inside of the dish card, go ahead and take what we've just learned as far as
converting a component over to type script,
and then importing the defining components method and just defining the types with for the dish.
Working through this, I was curious how much of what we've just seen and implemented
is going to be similar when using the composition API.
A lot of things we're doing upfront right now is to basically accommodate the options API
because we do provide a lot of conventions with that.
Because for those of you who are using this keyword a lot,
and this is, as you know in JavaScript, is a diabolical concept.
So type script gets super super lost.
And we try our best to hack around that to make your lives easier.
But when it comes to composition API,
I'm hoping that people will feel like it's a more native integration with,
as far as using view with type script.
Now I see Gullina or apologize by the mispronounce that,
but I see that apparently it's not as easy to expect it.
So I would love to hear from you when the time comes and as we're going through that.
But in the meantime, I think let's go ahead and do the solution for the exercise.
Okay, so for those here in the dish card,
hopefully you didn't find this exercise too difficult.
But basically we're really repeating what we did before in the restaurant card.
So the first thing first is we want to use type script,
so we are going to do the language attribute.
And actually there was a great question earlier for those who might be nearer to view
is that this language attribute is not something that's specific to script.
Basically view tries to use a native attribute within its component,
single file component, as much as possible.
So the language attribute can also be used on style, for example.
It's commonly used like pre-processors, like laying sass, for example.
Over those that use pug might be laying pug.
And we'll see that actually the attributes inside of these single file component blocks
can be basically anything you want.
So people have done some pretty interesting things to create some custom attributes
and we'll be using one later on in the course to show you that.
Okay, next thing we got to do is we got to import the find component from view
because we got to tell type script, hey, we're using this options API component wrapper thing.
So please, this is what it is.
And so if you haven't hovered over it, you'll see that there's a lot going on in here.
And so, and that is because once again, we're trying to help type script navigate
all of the guard rails that we set up with options API.
Once we have that, we want to actually make sure that we have the type for the dish.
So all I'm going to do is go onto the dish page.
And we're going to grab the dish from up here.
And so as we can see here, I actually think I memorized it.
So we have a type of dish and that has an idea of string that has a name of string
and it has a status with string as well.
And that's all it is.
And so to actually apply that now to our object, this is where we're going to practice
our as type casting and we're going to want the prop type.
And so what we need to do is import that from view.
Now, something that actually worth noting though is you might have been,
you might have been compelled to do it like this originally.
And so this feels normal because it's how we typically import stuff within JavaScript.
But you'll notice though is that it's yelling at us because it's saying that this is not exactly
a traditional JavaScript value.
This is actually a type.
So as a result, it should be yelling you, but we basically,
whenever you see import type, it's because we're trying to tell like the compiler
that like, hey, this thing you can basically ignore.
You don't need to compile it into anything.
Okay, so now that we have the prop type, we're going to use a greater than less than single
and then pass that in.
And then we inspect now.
We can see that our dish is a prop type dish.
And that's all there is to it.